hard...
大変...
it hurts?
痛い?
Does it really hurt?
本当 に痛い?
it hurts?
痛い?
yes little
はい 少
Just?
し だけ?
it hurts
痛い
It's beautiful
綺 麗 ね
It hurts. Stop this first. Don't hide this either.
痛 い まずこっちやめて こっちも隠さないで
You don't want to put a bath here, right?
お風呂置いたくないでしょ、ここ
No.
ダメだよ
Well, I guess I'll just watch it.
じゃあ、見るだけにしようかな、
Well then.
じゃあ
By yourself?
自 分で?
Are you coming for a drink?
飲みに来るの?
Are you hiding something?
何か隠してるの?
Can I see your pants?
パンツ見ていい?
Oh no.
やば
Yay ba.
やーば
picture?
え?
Lend me a little.
ちょっと貸して
Yay ba.
やーば
why?
なんで?
Yay ba.
やーば
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Yay ba.
やーば
I told you to look at my underwear.
下着見るって言ったじゃん
picture?
え?
Maybe I should go pick it up.
拾いに行っちゃおうかな
Hey, it's really bad.
ねぇ、ほんとにやだ
It's like good morning.
おはようしみたいな
Can I see it?
見ていいですか?
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
No way.
やだ
Just smell it.
匂い嗅ぐだけ
Okay.
いいよ
So, how about legs?
じゃあ 足ならいい?
What do you mean by feet?
足ってどういうこと?
feet.
足
You look amazing.
すごい顔してる
why?
なんで?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Gui.
グイって
I wonder if I can't see it.
見えんのかな、なんか
The soles of my feet are slightly black at the bottom.
ちょっと足の裏黒くなってるぐらいの下下が
You're lying.
嘘つけー
Really, really?
ほんとほんと?
I'm curious about that too.
そっちも気になるんだよね
please.
お願い
Really.
ほんとに
Really?
ほんとに?
Really.
ほんとに
What do you mean really?
ほんとにって言うのは?
Really.
ほんとに
Does that mean it's absolutely no good?
絶対ダメってこと?
Yeah.
うん
Can I take a sneak peek later?
後で、こっそり見ていい?
Why do you look like that?
なんでそういう顔するんだの?
no.
いや
Isn't that embarrassing?
恥ずかしいってことでしょ?
no.
いや
I just really hate it.
普通にほんとにもう嫌
Why are you showing me your bottom like this?
こうやって下を見せてくれるのに?
That's fine, right? I took it off.
そっちじゃいいってことでしょ、脱いだってことは
Look at it.
見してよ
Hands on the sides.
手は横
I'll do this myself, I'll put my hands through it from here.
自分でこう、ここから手を通してさ
Pussy.
おまんこ
Open your pussy.
おまんこ開いてみて
Do you want to see it properly?
ちゃんと見たいか?
Make it beautiful.
綺麗にさ
Let's put your butt out a little more.
もうちょっとお尻前出してこう
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるからさ
You want to rent it right away, right?
すぐ終わって借りたいでしょ?
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるからさ
Move it.
動かして
Open or close.
開いたり閉じたり
Do this with both hands.
両手でこう
Mom
お ま
Hmm, it's small.
ん こちっちゃいね
what happened?
どうしたの?
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
why?
なんで?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
I'm used to it, but does it hurt?
慣れてるけど痛いの?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
Would you like a little more?
もうちょっといい?
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるからさ
it hurts?
痛い?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
Wouldn't it be better to lick it?
舐めるほうがだったらいい?
Wait, it'll be over soon.
ちょっと、すぐ終わるからさ
The tip is also a little jiggly.
ちょっと、先端もぷるぷる
lick.
舐める
Just spit it out.
そのまま吐くって
All the way to the back.
ずっと奥までさ
This is the only place I can get into my mouth.
ここしか口に入ってないから
Go a little longer.
もうちょっといけ
why?
なんで?
Have you never done it?
したことないの?
mouth.
口
Because I can't stand it.
我慢できないからさ
Enough already.
もういいで
It's built in a good place.
いいとこにできてます
It's very narrow.
すごい狭い
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
it hurts?
痛い?
I'm used to it, you know.
慣れてるよ、ほら
Does this area hurt?
この辺が痛いの?
this is?
これは?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Look, it feels good.
ほら、気持ちいい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Does it still hurt?
まだ痛い?
It doesn't hurt, right?
痛かないでしょ?
You don't hate it, right?
嫌じゃないでしょ?
difficult?
難しい?
You've never done it, right?
やったことないでしょ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Can I stretch my legs?
足を伸ばしていい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You don't hate it, right?
嫌じゃないでしょ?
It looks wet, so wet.
濡れてるようだな、びっちゃびっちゃ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
It'll be over soon.
もうすぐ終わるから
I put away my food and it feels good.
ご飯しまって、気持ちいい
Looks like I'm going.
行きそう
Great, I'm going.
やばい、行きそう
I'll make it.
なすよ
Yes, I'll go.
はい、行く
It's okay if you let it flow.
流せば大丈夫だから